idt.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy Policy | IDT

Your privacy is very important to us. Integrated Device Technology (“IDT”) adheres to the following privacy policy regarding its collection, use and dissemination of personal and non-personal information collected through its website (idt.com). 

## Collection of Non-Personal Information

Whenever you visit a web page on the internet, your browser automatically identifies the IP address you were located at when you initiated your page request.  It also volunteers certain basic information like browser type, the operating system you are running, and in some cases the page that  referred you to the Site.  IDT’s server automatically collects this information and tracks it on a page by page and on a statistical basis.  Our server also collects date and time of visit; web page viewed; country, region, city, and company from where a page request was initiated; whether our site was accessed from a bookmark or a link; search keywords used; and the referring URL.

## Use of Non-Personal Information

IDT uses non-personal information such as the region or country of the world from which your IP request started to suggest the appropriate language  or  best promotion aligned to that region of the world. We also use browser type, operating system, and page visits for statistical analysis of site usage and navigation trends.

## Collection of Personal Information

When you create your personal preferences at IDT, we will ask for your name, title, company name, e-mail address, mail address and IDT product preferences. IDT also uses “Cookies” to collect personal information about our visitors.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We maintain the personal information described above for statistical purposes to improve our web site for users’ needs, to offer services, to administer the site, to correspond with users and for other purposes related to the reason you visited our site. IDT will only  give or sell this information to third parties to assist in providing information or services to you or to manage and improve the site and database. For example, IDT may provide your name and delivery address to third parties that IDT uses for delivering products to you.  IDT will also respond to legal requests for information where required by law.

## Cookies

Our site utilizes cookie technology to authenticate your access to some areas of our website and to prevent you from having to enter redundant and duplicate data.  Cookies also allow us to analyze user trends  to better understand your needs.  Cookies are small text files that our website places on your hard drive for identification purposes.  A cookie can contain information such as the URL you came from, your computer’s IP address (i.e., the Internet address of your computer) and domain type (e.g., “.com”, “.org”, etc.), your browser type, the country, state, and telephone area code where your server is located, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit, and any search terms that you entered on our site.  Cookies are a common web site practice. They cannot access, read or modify any data on your computer or provide us with your personal data. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies, although it is possible that some areas of our web site will not function properly if you do so.

IDT and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someone’s past visits to our website. IDT uses data from Google’s interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics. You may opt-out to prevent your data from being used by IDT and Google Analytics here at [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) .

## Correspondence and Notifications

When you create your IDT profile on the site, you can complete a personal interest profile. Where possible, IDT uses this personal interest profile and the information it gathers about  your activity on the site  via cookies to align the information delivered to your browser with  your interest preferences. IDT also will use your interest profile and your activity on the site to communicate with you via e-mail or to make offers to you during your visits. If you wish to stop receiving emails from IDT, we will terminate the activity upon receipt of your request as per the CAN-SPAM act. All of our email correspondence will provide the ability for users to unsubscribe.

## External Links

The Site contains links to third party sites. IDT does not endorse, sponsor or control those websites. Therefore, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites you link to via the IDT website.

## Security

When you transact business with IDT, our goal is to ensure that your information is transmitted across the web using certain security measures.  We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which encrypts sensitive information such as your name, address, phone number, credit card, etc. The IDT.com web site also uses digital certificates which allow your browser to confirm that the server you are transacting with is IDT’s server.  During the transaction, the server is identified to your browser and the information is encrypted before your personal information is transmitted.

Access to your personal information is limited to IDT employees and its services providers as described above. All personal information is protected through password access, which is only made available to identified corporate users.

We actively monitor and enhance our security on an ongoing basis, implementing website security technologies such as secure servers, firewalls, and encryption of financial data, to protect the safety of your personal data.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy.  However, we will not materially change our policies or  practices to make them less protective of customer information without notifying affected customers by email.  Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and the  user account you create on IDT.com.  We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how IDT is protecting your information.

## Comments

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy please email[ webmaster@idt.com](mailto:%20webmaster@idt.com).  You privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to address your concerns.
